Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Administrative records maintained by Henry Chauncey, Jr., 1972-1980; Accession 1983-A-036
  - Correspondence and Subject Files
    - South Central Community College (Box 18)
      - Budget, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 356)
      - Regional Advisory Council, 1976-1978 (Box 18, Folder 357)
    - United Way (Box 19)
      - Admissions Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 358)
      - Allocations, 19781977 (Box 19, Folder 359)
      - Annual Report, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 360)
      - Beers Clinic, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 361)
      - Board Committees, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 362)
      - Board members, list of, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 363)
      - Budget, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 364)
      - By-laws Revision Committee, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 365)
      - Campaign, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 366 - 367)
      - Cancer, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 368)
      - Combined Health Agencies, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 369)
      - Committees, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 370)
      - Communications Committee, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 371)
      - Communications Services, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 372)
      - Consortium for Youth, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 373)
      - Data Board, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 374)
      - Development Assistance, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 375)
      - Endowment, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 376)
      - Executive Committee, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 377)
      - Finance Committee, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 378)
      - Financial, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 379)
      - Fuel Bank, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 380)
      - Fuel Crisis, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 381)
      - General, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 383)
      - Grantsmanship, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 384)
      - Homemaker Services, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 385)
      - Info-Line, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 386)
      - Labor Agency, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 387)
      - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (LEAA), undated (Box 20, Folder 388 - 389)
      - Member Agencies Memoranda of Understanding, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 390)
      - Memoranda, minutes, 1975-1978 (Box 21, Folder 391 - 392)
      - Minutes, Budget, memoranda, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 393)
      - National, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 394)
      - New Campaign, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 395)
      - New Haven Foundation, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 396)
      - New Haven Register, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 397)
      - Nominating Committee, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 398)
      - Olin Corporation, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 399)
      - Pension, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 400)
      - Personnel, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 401)
      - Release, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 402)
      - President: problems, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 403)
      - Problems, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 404)
      - Register story, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 405)
      - Retarded Citizens, Association for, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 406)
      - Salute to Giamatti, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 407)
      - State meeting, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 409)
      - Visiting Nurse Association, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 410)
      - YMCA (Young Men's Christian Association), 1978 (Box 21, Folder 411)
      - Youth Consortium, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 412)
    - Yale New Haven Hospital (Box 22)
      - Accreditation, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 413)
      - Ad Hoc Committee, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 414)
      - Board, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 415 - 416)
      - Garage over connector, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 417)
      - Medical Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 418)
      - New hospital, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 419 - 421)
      - Park City Hospital, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 422)
      - Role of the hospital, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 423)
      - United Illuminating Company, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 424)
      - St. Raphael, Hospital of, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 425)
    - Yale New Haven Medical Center (Box 23, Folder 426)
      - Board, 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 427)
      - Development Committee, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 428)
      - Campaign Executive Committee, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 429)
      - Neurology: contribution, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 431)
      - United Illuminating Company, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 432)
    - Yale University Press: Board of Governors, 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 433 - 434)
- Reports submitted to the secretary, 1953-1979; Accession 1984-A-020
  - University Council Reports
    - Art and Architecture, 1964 May 1 -1972 December 1 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 10)
    - Art Gallery and British Art Center, 1973 May 4 - 1976 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 11 - 14)
    - Art Gallery, 1970 December 4 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Art Gallery and British Art Center, 1963 December 6 - 1967 December 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Art Gallery, 1968 April 26 - 1976 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 17 - 19)
    - Art Gallery, 1972 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 20 - 24)
    - Athletics, 1965 April 30 - 1977 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 25 - 32)
    - Community Relations, 1963 December 6 - 1974 May 3 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Divinity School and Department of Religious Studies, 1964 May 1 - 1965 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 34 - 41)
    - Drama, 1963 December 6 - 1971 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 42 - 48)
    - Engineering, 1969 December 5 - 1970 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 49 - 51)
    - Forestry, 1949 June - 1968 April 26 (Box 2, Folder 52 - 61)
    - Graduate School, 1963 December 6 - 1972 May 12 (Box 2, Folder 62 - 68)
    - Humanities, 1964 May 1 - 1970 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 69 - 70)
    - Law School, 1953 August 1 - 1975 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 71 - 78)
    - Library, 1963 December 6 - 1973 November 30 (Box 2, Folder 79 - 83)
    - Medical Affairs, 1953 August 1 0 1975 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 84 - 88)
    - Peabody Museum, 1963 December 6 - 1973 November 30 (Box 2, Folder 89 - 99)
  - Publications, 1965 April 30 - 1971 May 7 (Box 3, Folder 100 - 106)
  - Sciences - Physical, 1975 May 2 - 1978 May 5 (Box 3, Folder 107 - 110)
  - Social Sciences, 1969 April 25 - 1972 December 1 (Box 3, Folder 111 - 114)
  - Social Sciences - Policy, 1975 December 5 - 1977 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 115 - 116)
  - Divinity School and Department of Religious Studies, 1977 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Yale College, 1964 December 4 - 1970 May (Box 3, Folder 118 - 124)
  - Brochure: The Fourth International Congress on the Enlightenment and the Sixth Annual Meeting of the American Society for Eighteenth Century Studies, 1975 July 13-20 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Brochure: The Fourth International Congress on the Enlightenment, 1974 June 4 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Photographs Sent to Yale Photographs Collection, YRG 48, 1948-1980 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Corporation Budget Committee Minutes, 1970 September 25 - 1971 November 5 (Box 4, Folder 132 - 135)
  - Report to the Yale Alumni on Alumni Activities, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 136 - 138)
  - Coaches Manual, 1975 October 9 (Box 4, Folder 139 - 140)
  - A case study in Admissions, Yale University Department of Undergraduate Admissions, Fall, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 141 - 142)
  - Exploratory Studies in Undergraduate Admissions, Yale University Office of Institutional Research, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Operations Improvement Program for the Office of Undergraduate Admissions of Yale University, 1972 March 16 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Admissions and Financial Aid (graduate and professional schools only), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 145 - 147)
- Records maintained by Henry Chauncey, Jr., 1969-1973; Accession 1990-A-060
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Athletic Association, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chauncey memos regarding admissions, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Clippings: Journal Courier
    - 1971 Aug - Sep (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1971 Oct (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1971 Nov (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1972 Jan (Box 1, Folder 6 - 7)
  - Community Relations, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Duncan Hotel, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Elderly, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - General Bulletin
    - 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 11 - 12)
    - 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 13 - 14)
  - Identifications, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Connecticut Junior Science and Humanities Symposia
    - Report of the Fifth, 1968 April 25-26 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, agenda, and minutes, 1968- 1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - General Information Bulletin: Sixth JSHS, 1969 April 7-8 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Report of the Sixth, 1969 April 7-8 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, agenda and minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Program of the Seventh, 1970 April 6-7 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Report of the Seventh, 1970 April 6-7 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Program and report of the Eighth, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Correspondence and subject files of Linda Lorimer, 1979-2006; Accession 2007-A-226
  Restricted until January, 1, 2041
- Honorary degree records, 1991-2003; Accession 2008-A-087
  Restricted until Jan, 1, 2038
  - NOMINATIONS
    - A-D, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - D-L, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - M-R, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - S -Z, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - WORKING PAPERS
    - ADDRESSES and BIOGRAPHIES, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - ACCOMODATIONS, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Program and photo order, provost's presentation, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - CAPS AND GOWNS, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - THANK YOU LFTTERS, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - WORKING PAPERS, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - CITATIONS, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - DIPLOMAS, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - LUNCHEON, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - HONORARY DEGREES
  - MEETINGS (Box 1, Folder 30 - 32)
  - NOMINATIONS
    - A - O, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - P - Z, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - COCKTAIL PARTY AND DINNER, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - THANK YOU LETTERS, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - DIPLOMAS, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - ACCOMODATIONS, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - LUNCHEON, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - PROG. AND PHOTO ORDER, PROVOST'S PRESENTATION, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - TRANSPORTATION, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - NOMINATIONS
    - A-D, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - E-G, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - H-L, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - M-P, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Q-T, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - U-Z, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - HONORARY DEGREES
    - 1989
      - ADDRESSES AND BIOGRAPHIES, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 63)
      - CITATIONS, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - 1992
      - RESPONSES, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65)
      - INVITATION RESPONSE, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 66)
      - COMMITTEE, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 82)
      - Meetings
        - 1992 Apr (Box 2, Folder 89)
        - 1992 Sep (Box 2, Folder 90)
        - 1992 Nov (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - 1993
      - HONORARY DEGREES COMMITTEE, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 92)
      - COMMITTEE, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 93)
      - RESPONSES, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - 1989
      - CAP AND GOWNS, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 103)
      - HD MASTER CHART, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 104)
      - COMMITTEE MEETINGS, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 105 - 108)
      - WORKING PAPERS, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 109)
      - COMMITTEE, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 1990
      - NOMINATIONS, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 111)
      - ADDRESSES AND BIOGRAPHIES, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 124)
      - COMMITTEE, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 125)
      - Meetings
        - 1990 Jun (Box 3, Folder 126)
        - 1990 Aug (Box 3, Folder 127)
        - 1990 Sep (Box 3, Folder 128)
        - 1990 Dec (Box 3, Folder 129)
      - CAPS and GOWNS, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 130)
      - LUNCHEON, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 131)
      - ACCOMODATIONS, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 132)
      - RECIPIENTS, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - 1989-1990 Honorary Degrees (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - 1990
      - DINNER, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 135)
      - WORKING PAPERS, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 136)
      - THANK YOUS, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 137)
      - PROGRAM and PHOTO ORDER, PROVOST'S PRESENTATION, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 138)
      - CITATIONS (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - 1991
      - BACKGROUND MATERIALS - RECIPIENTS, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 140)
      - A - H, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 141)
      - COMMITTEE, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 142)
      - Meetings
        - 1990 Nov 30 (Box 3, Folder 155)
        - 1990 Sep 17 (Box 3, Folder 156)
        - 1990 Apr 6 (Box 3, Folder 157)
        - 1990 Jun (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - 1991
      - BIOGRAPHIES, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 159)
      - CITATIONS, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 160)
      - COMMENCEMENT, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 161)
      - CAPS and GOWNS, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 162)
      - HOSPITALITY, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 163)
      - WORKING PAPERS, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - CORPORATION CHRON FILE, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - CORPORATION CHRON FILE, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - Development and Alumni Affairs, 1996-2000 (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - AUDIT COMMITTEE, 1992-2002 (Box 4, Folder 168 - 170)
  - Buildings and Grounds COMMITTEE, 1993-2001 (Box 4, Folder 171 - 172)
  - BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 173)
  - COMPENSATION COMMITTEE, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 174)
  - CORPORATION COMMITTEES, 1996-2001 (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - Educational Policy Committee (EPC), 1995-2001 (Box 4, Folder 176)
  - FINANCE COMMITTEE, 1993-2001 (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - HONORARY DEGREES COMMITTEE, 1995-2001 (Box 4, Folder 178 - 179)
  - INSTITUTIONAL POLICIES COMMITTEE, 1995-2001 (Box 4, Folder 180 - 181)
- Diploma, degree and award records, 1991-2003; Accession 2008-A-088
  - 2003 Feb 8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 2003 Apr 12 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 2003 May 26 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 2003 Jun 4 Law (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 2003 Jun 6 Law (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 2003 Jun 30 Law (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 2003 Aug 6 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 2003 Sep 15 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 2003 Oct 4 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 2003 Dec 6 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 2002 Jan 2 Nursing (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 2002 Feb 9 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 2002 Apr 13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 2002 Jun 5 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 2002 Jun 7 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 2002 Sep 9 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 2002 Sep 27-28 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 2002 Dec 7 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 2001 Feb 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 2001 Apr 20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 2001 Jun 8 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 2001 Jun 16 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 2001 Sep 10 Master of Med. Sc (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 2001 Oct 1 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 2001 Dec 8 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 2000 Feb 1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 2000 Apr 1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 2000 May 31 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 2000 May 31 Law (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 2000 Jun 28 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 2000 Sep 1 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 2000 Sep 11 Master of Med. Sc. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 2000 Dec 2 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 1999 Feb 20 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 1999 Apr 10 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - 1999 Jun 2 Law (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - 1999 Jun 11 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - 1999 Oct 2 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - 1999 Dec 1 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - 1998 Feb 21 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 1998 Apr 18 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - 1998 Jun 19 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - 1998 Sep 1 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - 1998 Dec 5 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - 1997 Feb 22 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - 1997 Apr 12 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - 1997 Jun 13 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - 1997 Sep 1 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - 1997 Nov 22 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - 1996 Jan 12 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - 1996 Feb 3 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - 1996 Apr 20 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - 1996 Jun 8 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - 1996 Sep 27 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - 1996 Dec 7 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - 1995 Feb 25 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - 1995 Apr 1 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - 1995 Jun 23 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - 1995 Aug 21 Physician Associate (PA) Certificates (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - 1995 Sep 24 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - 1995 Nov 17 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - 1994 Jan 21 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - 1994 Feb 26 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - 1994 Apr 16 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - 1994 Jun 25 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - 1994 Aug 29 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - 1994 Sep 24 PA Certificates (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - 1994 Dec 10 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - 1993 Jan 16 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - 1993 Feb 27 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - 1993 Apr 17 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - 1993 Jun 26 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - 1993 Aug 30 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - 1993 Oct 2 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - 1993 Nov 20 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - 1992 Jan 11 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - 1992 Feb 1 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - 1992 Apr 11 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - 1992 Jun 26 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - 1992 Aug 1 PA Program (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - 1992 Sep 29 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - 1992 Nov 14 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - 1991 Jan 1 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - 1991 Mar 2 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - 1991 Apr 1 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - 1991 May 27 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - 1991 Jun 1 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - 1991 Sep 28 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - 1991 Nov 16 (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Diploma records, 1990-2006; Accession 2008-A-155
  Restricted until Jan, 1, 2042
  - B.A./B.S., 1990 May 28, June 5 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Professional/Grad., 1990 May 28, June 5 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1990 Jun -1991 Apr (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - B.A./B.S., 1991 May 27, June 4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Professional/Grad., 1991 May 27, June 4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1991 Jun -1992 Apr (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - B.A./B.S., 1992 May 25, June 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Professional/Grad., 1992 May 25, June 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1992 Jun -1993 Apr (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - B.A./B.S., 1993 May 24, June 2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Professional/Grad., 1993 May 24, June 2 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1993 Jun -1994 Apr (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - B.A./B.S., 1994 May 23, June 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Professional/Grad., 1994 May 23, June 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1994 Jun -1995 Apr (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - B.A./B.S., 1995 May 22, May 31 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Professional/Grad., 1995 May 22, May 31 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1995 Jun -1996 Apr (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - B.A./B.S., 1996 May 27, June 5 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Professional/Grad., 1996 May 27, June 5 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1996 Jun -1997 Apr (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - B.A./B.S., 1997 May 26, June 4 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Professional/Grad., 1997 May 26, June 4 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 1997 Jun -1998 Apr (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - B.A./B.S., 1998 May 25, June 3 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Professional/Grad., 1998 May 25, June 3 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 1998 Jun -1999 Apr (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - B.A./B.S., 1999 May 24, June 2 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 1999 Professional/Grad., 1999 May 24, June 2 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 1999 Jun -2000 Apr (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - B.A./B.S., 2000 May 22, May 31 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Professional/Grad., 2000 May 22, May 31 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - 2000 Jun -2001 Apr (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - B.A./B.S., 2001 May 21, May 30 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Professional/Grad., 2001 May 21, May 30 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - 2001 Jun -2002 Apr (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - B.A./B.S., 2002 May 27, June 5 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Professional/Grad., 2002 May 27, June 5 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - 2002 Jun -2003 Apr (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - B.A./B.S., 2003 May 26, June 4 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Professional/Grad., 2003 May 26, June 4 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 2003 Jun -2004 Apr (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - B.A./B.S., 2004 May 24, June 7 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Professional/Grad., 2004 May 24, June 7 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 2004 Jun-2005 Apr (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - B.A./B.S., 2005 May 23, June 1 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Professional/Grad., 2005 May 23, June 1 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - 2005 Jun -2006 Apr (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Records concerning Yale licensed trademarks and the Freshman Assembly, 1972-2005; Accession 2012-A-062
  Restricted until January 1, 2040
  This accession contains the files of Denise Castellano, Assistant Secretary, Office of Marketing and Trademark Licensing
  - Licensing, 2001-2005
    - Yale Artwork 2001: Yale Bulldogs, Seal (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Yale Artwork 2002: Yale, etc. (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
    - Yale Artwork - Athletic Bulldog, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Yale Artwork - Yale Seal, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Yale Artwork 2003: Yale Bulldogs, Seal (Box 2, Folder 7-9)
    - Yale Artwork 2003 Part 2: Yale Bulldogs, Seal (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
    - Yale Artwork 2004: Yale Bulldogs, Seal (Box 3, Folder 12-16)
    - Artwork - September 2004, 2004 September (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Artwork - September 2004, 2004 September (Box 4, Folder 18-20)
    - Artwork 2005 (Box 4, Folder 21-22)
    - Artwork 2005 (Box 5, Folder 23-25)
  - Freshman Assembly, 1972-2005
    - 1972-1974 September (Box 5, Folder 26-28)
    - 1975-1979 September (Box 6, Folder 29-33)
    - 1980-1984 September (Box 6, Folder 34-38)
    - 1990-1996 August (Box 7, Folder 39-45)
    - 1997-2001 (Box 8, Folder 46-50)
    - 2001 Req's (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - 2002 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - 2002 Req's (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - 2002 Ushers (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - 2003 February - October 11 (Box 9, Folder 55-59)
    - 2004 August 28 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - 2004 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - 2004 Ushers (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - 2005 (Box 10, Folder 63-65)
    - 2005 Law Signs (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - 2005 Marching Order (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - 2005 Program (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - 2005 To Do (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - 2005 Ushers (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - 2005 Woolsey Signs (Box 10, Folder 71)
- Records of the Office of Marketing and Trademark Licensing, 1998-2007; Accession 2012-A-080
  Restricted until January 1, 2042.
  The 2012-A-080 accession contains records from the Fair Labor Association and the Workers Rights Coalition regarding its advocacy work with the Office of Marketing and Trademark Licensing against the use of sweatshops.
  - Fair Labor Association/Workers Rights Consortium, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Fair Labor Association, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Fair Labor Association, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fair Labor Association/Workers Rights Consortium, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Fair Labor Association - Task Force Committee, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fair Labor Association, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Workers Rights Consortium, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "Sweatshop info" for Richard C. Levin, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Fair Labor Association/University Advisory Council, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Workers Rights Consortium, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Fair Labor Association, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Sweatshops - Richard C. Levin material, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Sweatshops, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fair Labor Association - General and other, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Sweatshops - General, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Sweatshops - General, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 16-18)
  - Workers Rights Consortium, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 19-20)
  - Sweatshops - Petitions and mass e-mails, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Fair Labor Association, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 22-23)
  - Sweatshops - Richard C. Levin Communications to Students, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Sweatshops - Nina Glickson memos, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Fair Labor Association, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 26-27)
  - Digital Yale: University Council Committee, 2007December 9-10 (Box 3, Folder 29)